How can you guys become welcome back to my channel,
so in today's video you will be updated about
National Policy, as you know
subscribe to this channel and
for subscription I am going to tell you one thing,
Insurance Regulatory Authority
of India has launched a project which you can
subscribe to, so in 10 12 15 days this
policy will be launched in the market, you can
see the subscribe button where you will
get the option to apply, if
you have a President Market Question, then
whenever you take your policy, it is provided to you
on a specific person or clearly basis,
like my own
policy bond was for one year, which is going to be
different and the second
liability which
subscribes to the channel is that if you work to hurt someone
and want to buy a government vehicle, you stay
out of the city for a lot of time in connection with your work, like how is it with me, I
myself stay out for a lot of time, so the
running speed of the vehicle is very less or
you use public transport more,
so basically a policy for those people
who drive a vehicle, as long as the tomato is there,
you can see this  In this you will get the
option of how many kilometers you want to
subscribe, here you should subscribe for more than kilometers,
after that
I understand the subscription, then subscribe for very less kilometers and
clear it, then you will have to pay only a
little more PM in it and
before the kilometers expire, you
make a plan, if you have to go on a long-term, then
you can also get your policy changed,
you can use our normal standard policy
in that policy or
you can increase it by your kilometers, so
all these facilities will be included in the policy,
secondly, by coming like this,
you also take any policy related to your liability by editing it
along with the kilometers, then the liability in case
of the policy also expires
according to the third kilometer and you have taken a policy for 1 year
that within one year I will
drive the metro, second kilometer but you
drive 10 kilometers, but the third party
liability point will be
covered in it and it is not that if you
activate your third kilometer then the
third party liability thing will be
covered, competing Indian Akshay
Insurance companies and people told that
you can activate your third kilometer by accident  You go
but still the liability will
remain with your balance and to refill
you will have to do the same as sports news
which is that you will start getting the reading of your audio meter
and if there is no such thing then
definitely subscribe and it is not necessary to renew the
policy of the appointed subscription about this policy, the
youth can
definitely subscribe
and how much discount are you getting in this policy, if you subscribe then
you can select
your friend, you
can use the slide of tension kilometer and accordingly
your free will increase a little but still it should be
less than what we decide now, so this is a very
good bonding for yourself, you will have to subscribe for yourself,
I have subscribed to you for a long time in this quarter
inch and
subscription means that if something else happens then it has been
completely launched, friends if you
like this video then do not forget to share it,
important information and
subscribe from
going to the office because like me and like you
many people drive the car less
and accordingly you can take your policy
and your cream  If you can reduce it
then please share this information
with maximum people and if you have
not subscribed then please meet me in the comments,
I will tell you more with some more information.